Guide To the University Of California, Santa Cruz Contemporary Classical Collection ARS.0103
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 7" reels, 118 audiotape reel(s)
  - Offenbach: La Perichole. Mozart: Don Giovani, 1971; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips; mono; four track] (Box 9, Reel 20)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Don Giovanni. Uppman, baritone. Krips, conductor. Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.). March 20, 1971.
    Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Périchole. Uppman, baritone. Richard, Cyril. Metropolitan Opera Chorus, Allers, conductor. Complete performance except for the opening bars of the Overture. Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.). January 23, 1971.
    Allers, Franz; Krips, Josef; Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.). Chorus; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880; Ritchard, Cyril, 1897-1977; Uppman, Theodor, 1920-2005
  - Cabrillo Festival 1970, 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 21)
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Symphonie de Psaumes.
    Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Concerto, harpsichord, instrumental ensemble.
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Invencion. Rodríguez, piano.
    Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945. Tót népdalok, mixed voices, piano. Cabrillo Festival Chorus, Seeley, conductor. August 29, 1970.
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. A woman is a worthy thing. Cabrillo Festival Chorus, Seeley, conductor. August 29, 1970.
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Nocturnes, mixed voices. Cabrillo Festival Chorus, Seeley, conductor. August 29, 1970.
    Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Old American songs, set 1. Simple gifts. Cabrillo Festival Chorus, Seeley, conductor. August 29, 1970.
    Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Amor brujo. Pantomima. Petersen, mezzo-soprano; Chavez, conductor.
    Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Music for the theatre. Chavez, conductor.
    Seeley, Gilbert; Rodríguez, María Teresa; Petersen, Donna; Cabrillo Festival Chorus; Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945; Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978; Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990; Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971
  - Harpsichord recital by Igor Kipnis at the Free Music Store, New York City, 1970-01-29; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 22)
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Suites, harpsichord, HWV 430, E major. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Greensleeves. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1724). Cyclopes. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1729-1730). Gavotte avec 6 doubles. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1729-1730). Triomphante. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1729-1730). Fanfarinette. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord. Selections. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Rorem, Ned, 1923- Spiders. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Edmunds, Christopher. Suite, 1950. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Toccatas, harpsichord, BWV 911, C minor. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Sonatas, piano, H. XVI, 13, E major. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Kuhnau, Johann, 1660-1722. Biblische Historien. Combattimento trà David e Goliath. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667. Suites, keyboard instrument, no. 26, B minor. Kipnis, harpsichord.
    Dandrieu, Jean François, 1682-1738; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667; Edmunds, Christopher; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Rorem, Ned, 1923-; Kuhnau, Johann, 1660-1722; Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764; Kipnis, Igor
  - Class 7-13-60 (recital Heinitz and Ehlers), 1960-07-13; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 9, Reel 23)
    Heinitz, Eva; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981
  - Cabrillo Festival, 1971 and 1973, 1971-1973; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 24)
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Bœuf sur le toit
    Ruggles, Carl, 1876-1971. Portals.
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Cinéma-fantaisie.
    Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 2, op. 83, B♭ major. Cabrillo Festival Orchestra, Chavez, conductor. 1973. Soloist not noted.
    Roussel, Albert, 1869-1937. Festin de l'araignée. Selections. Cabrillo Festival Orchestra, Chavez, conductor. 1973.
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Instrumental miniatures. Cabrillo Festival Orchestra, Chavez, conductor. 1973.
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Pirámide. Elements. Chavez, conductor. 1971.
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Caballos de vapor. Suite Chavez, conductor. 1971.
    Satie, Erik, 1866-1925. Petites pièces montées. Chavez, conductor. 1971.
    Cabrillo Festival Orchestra; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Satie, Erik, 1866-1925; Ruggles, Carl, 1876-1971; Roussel, Albert, 1869-1937; Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974; Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978; Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897
  - Concert at Berkeley Piano Club and various other performance extracts, 1973-07-21; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips; dolby] (Box 9, Reel 25)
    Contents note
    The contents of this tape are noted on two small pieces of paper found with the recording. These handwritten notes are illegible in parts. The program note presented for this recording is therefore a partial listing of the contents, based on what could be deciphered from these handwritten notes.
    Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Marches et un intermède. Tafelmusik Baroque Orchestra.
    Tailleferre, Germaine, 1892-1983. Concertinos, harp, orchestra. Badings, harp.
    Honegger, Arthur, 1892-1955. Symphonies, no. 2. Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, Goldberg, conductor. 1942.
    Crumb, George. Black angels.
    Buel, Charles. From the Deep Blue Eastern Realm of Pre-Eminent Happiness. First performance.
    Lentz, Daniel, 1942-. Sermon.
    Seeger, Ruth Crawford, 1901-1953. Quartet, violins (2), viola, cello.
    Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997. Preludes, violins (2), viola, cello
    Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Septet, piano, clarinet, horn, bassoon, violin, viola, cello.
    Weill, Kurt, 1900-1950. Work not noted.
    Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983. Work not noted.
    Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962. Two songs. Dudley, soprano.
    Badings, Vera; Tafelmusik Baroque Orchestra; Goldberg, Szymon, 1909-1993; Tailleferre, Germaine, 1892-1983; Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997; Nederlands Kamerorkest; Honegger, Arthur, 1892-1955; Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963; Buel, Charles; Dudley, Anna Carol; Ibert, Jacques, 1890-1962; Crumb, George; Weill, Kurt, 1900-1950; Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Seeger, Ruth Crawford, 1901-1953; Lentz, Daniel, 1942-
  - Sorabji; Badings: Quintet No.4, 1973-11-09; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips (side 1), 7.5 ips (side 2); stereo; dolby] (Box 9, Reel 26)
    Badings, Henk, 1907-1987. Quintets, no. 4. Pacific Wind. Live concert recording at 1750 Arch Street, Berkeley, CA.
    A discussion about Sorabji followed by piano works composed by him.
    Badings, Henk, 1907-1987; Sorabji, Kaikhosru Shapurji, 1892-1988; Pacific Wind
  - Hindemith: Sonata No.1 for organ, 1961-09-03; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 15 ips; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 27)
    Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963. Sonatas, organ, no. 1. Moe, organ. Played on the Holtkamp Organ in Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, California. Recorded by Dick McGraw. Sept 3, 1961.
    Moe, Lawrence, 1917-2013; Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963
  - Honegger: Sonatina for clarinet and piano. Dahl: Concerto a Tre. Kirchner: Trio for violin, cello and piano. Delius: Violin concerto, 1971; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips; starts mono then stereo] (Box 9, Reel 28)
    Delius, Frederick, 1862-1934. Concertos, violin, orchestra. Erickson, violin; Berkeley Free Orchestra, Cleve, conductor. September 21, 1971.
    Kirchner, Leon. Trios, piano, violin, cello, no. 1. Pacifica Chamber Players. August 15, 1971.
    Dahl, Ingolf, 1912-1970. Concerto a tre. Pacifica Chamber Players. August 15, 1971.
    Honegger, Arthur, 1892-1955. Sonatinas, clarinet, piano. Pacifica Chamber Players. August 15, 1971.
    Berkeley Free Orchestra; Kirchner, Leon; Honegger, Arthur, 1892-1955; Cleve, George, 1936-2015; Pacifica Chamber Players; Delius, Frederick, 1862-1934; Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997; Dahl, Ingolf, 1912-1970
  - Chávez; Mompou; Naumann; Peterson-Berger; Rimsky-Korsakov; Röntgen, circa 1969-1972; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips; mono; four track] (Box 9, Reel 29)
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Etudes, piano (1949). Rodríguez, piano. Aptos, CA. May 29, 1972.
    Röntgen, Julius, 1855-1932. Oud-nederlandse dansen. Concertgebouw orchestra, Mengelberg, conductor.
    Recital by Aloys and Alfons Kontarsky. Hertz Hall. January 10, 1969.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Impresiones íntimas. White, piano.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Scènes d'enfants. White, piano.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Trois comptines. Dudley, soprano; White, piano.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Quatre Melodies. Dudley, soprano; White, piano.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Le Nuage. Dudley, soprano; White, piano.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Charmes. White, piano.
    Naumann, Siegfried, 1919-2001. Risposte, no. 2. Wiberg, piano; Lanzky, organ; Bengtsson, guitar; Petersen, trombone; whole ensemble, percussion.
    Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Symphonies, no. 3, op. 32, C major. Moscow Radio Orchestra, Gauk, conductor.
    Peterson-Berger, Wilhelm, 1867-1942. Same Ätnam. Radio orchestra of Sweden, Fryberg, conductor.
    Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987. Paisajes. White, piano.
    Kontarsky, Aloys; Rodríguez, María Teresa; Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978; Mengelberg, Willem, 1871-1951; Mompou, Federico, 1893-1987; White, Julian, 1930-2006; Dudley, Anna Carol; Kontarsky, Alfons; Vsesoi͡uznoe radio. Bolʹshoĭ simfonicheskiĭ orkestr; Gauk, Aleksandr, 1893-1963; Naumann, Siegfried, 1919-2001; Lanzky, Otto; Radioorkestern (Sweden); Röntgen, Julius, 1855-1932; Frykberg, Sten, 1910-1983; Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908; Peterson-Berger, Wilhelm, 1867-1942; Concertgebouworkest
  - Riegger: Study in Sonority. Chávez: Piano Concerto, 1971; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 30)
    Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978. Concertos, piano, orchestra. Rodriguez, piano; Cabrillo Festival Orchestra, Chavez, conductor. Aptos, CA. August 22, 1971.
    Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961. Study in Sonority. San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Ozawa, conductor. May 7, 1971.
    Ozawa, Seiji, 1935-; Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978; Cabrillo Festival Orchestra; San Francisco Symphony Orchestra; Rodríguez, María Teresa; Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961
  - BBC Program, Music by Bach's Predecessors, circa 1962-1964; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 9, Reel 31)
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 1er livre. No 4. Curtis, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, Berkeley, CA. October 30, 1964.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 248, B♭ major. Curtis, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, Berkeley, CA. October 30, 1964.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 239, F minor. Curtis, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, Berkeley, CA. October 30, 1964.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 145, D major. Curtis, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, Berkeley, CA. October 30, 1964.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 3, A minor. Leonhardt, harpsichord.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 52, D minor. Leonhardt, harpsichord.
    Sweelinck, Jan Pieterszoon, 1562-1621. Toccata No.20. Leonhardt, harpsichord.
    Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Suite for harpsichord. Kind, harpsichord.
    Honegger, Arthur, 1892-1955. Seven short pieces for harpsichord. Kind, harpsichord.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 153, G major. Tagliavini, harpsichord.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 64, D minor. Tagliavini, harpsichord.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 2e livre. No 11. Fastes de la grande et ancienne Mxnxstrxndxsx. Kind, harpsichord. 1962 Ascona Festival.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1729-1730). Poule. Kind, harpsichord. 1962 Ascona Festival.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 3e livre. No 14. Rossignol-en-amour. Kind, harpsichord. 1962 Ascona Festival.
    Improvisation by Malcolm and Bream on chorale "Herzlich thut mich verlangen." 17th Aldeburgh Festival.
    Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667. Toccatas, keyboard instrument, no. 2, D minor. Malcolm, harpsichord. 17th Aldeburgh Festival.
    Content
    Reusner, Esaias, 1636-1679. Suites, lute, G minor. Bream, lute. 17th Aldeburgh Festival.
    Kuhnau, Johann, 1660-1722. Biblische Historien. Hiskia agonizzante e risanato. Malcolm, harpsichord. 17th Aldeburgh Festival.
    Honegger, Arthur, 1892-1955; Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963; Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725; Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757; Curtis, Alan; Leonhardt, Gustav, 1928-; Sweelinck, Jan Pieterszoon, 1562-1621; Froberger, Johann Jacob, 1616-1667; Reusner, Esaias, 1636-1679; Bream, Julian; Malcolm, George, 1917-1997; Tagliavini, Luigi Ferdinando; Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764; Kind, Silvia; Couperin, François, 1668-1733; Kuhnau, Johann, 1660-1722
  - KPFA live concert by Margaret Fabrizio, harpsichord, and George Houle, oboe, 1967-06-06; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 9, Reel 32)
    Fabrizio, Margaret; Houle, George
  - Francesco Trio, San Francisco Chamber Music Society. Lantz: Alpha, 1967; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 9, Reel 33)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Trios, piano, violin, cello, D. 898, B♭ major. Francesco Trio. San Francisco Chamber Music Society. February 20, 1967.
    Lantz, Christopher. Alpha, for soprano, clarinet, and piano. Premiere. KPFA broadcast. June 27, 1967.
    Kirchner, Leon. Sonata concertante. Francesco Trio. San Francisco Chamber Music Society. February 20, 1967.
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Trios, piano, violin, cello, K. 502, B♭ major. Francesco Trio. San Francisco Chamber Music Society. February 20, 1967.
    Francesco Trio; Kirchner, Leon; Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828; Lantz, Christopher; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
  - Bloch; Thompson; Stein; Kirchner: an unknown Belgian composer, circa 1971-1972; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips] (Box 9, Reel 34)
    Trio by an unnamed Belgian composer. Festival of Belgium. July 21, 1972.
    Kirchner, Leon. Trios, piano, violin, cello, no. 1. Francesco Trio. Oakland Museum. March 12, 1971.
    Thomson, Virgil, 1896-1989. Capital capitals. Brewer, Hammer, Fleck, and Shields, vocals; Cobb, piano. Oakland Museum. March 12, 1971.
    Bloch, Ernest, 1880-1959. Suites, cello, no. 1. Hampton, cello.
    Kirchner, Leon; Bloch, Ernest, 1880-1959; Thomson, Virgil, 1896-1989; Stein, Gertrude, 1874-1946; Hammer, David; Brewer, Bruce, 1944-; Shields, James; Cobb, Donald; Francesco Trio; Fleck, William
  - Bach, Bach, Clementi, Couperin, Handel, Haydn, Moran, Mozart, Rameau, Purcell, Scarlatti, 1967-1970; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; mono; four track] (Box 9, Reel 35)
    Recital by Jean Nandi, harpsichord. October, 1970.
    Clementi, Muzio, 1752-1832. Rondo. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, piano, K. 331, A major. Alla turca. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Sonata in E flat. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Clementi, Muzio, 1752-1832. Sonatas, piano, op. 25. No. 5. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788. Rondos, keyboard instrument, H. 268, G major. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Rondos, piano, K. 511, A minor. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Clementi, Muzio, 1752-1832. Sonatas and duet, op. 12. Sonata, no. 2. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Fantasien, piano, K. 397, D minor. Fabrizio, square piano. April 10, 1969.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonatas, violin, harpsichord, BWV 1016, E major. Reller, violin; Fabrizio, harpsichord. San Francisco College for Women. March 17, 1969.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord. Selections. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Italienisches Konzert. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 2e livre. No 11. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1724). Tendres plaintes. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin (1724). Joyeuse. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Handel, George Frederic, 1685-1759. Suite, F. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Purcell, Daniel, -1717. Toccata, harpsichord, A minor. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Französische Ouvertüre, B minor. Kraus, harpsichord. KPFA broadcast.
    Moran, Robert, 1937-. Scream Kiss No.1, for harpsichord and tape. Fabrizio, harpsichord. World premiere. De Young Museum, San Francisco, CA. August, 1968.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 2e livre. No 8. Schwandt, harpsichord.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, harpsichord, BWV 818, A minor. Schwandt, harpsichord. Recorded at Schwandt's Palo Alto, CA studio. September or November, 1967.
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Suite, F. Kirkpatrick, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. January 12, 1969.
    Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757; Schwandt, Erich; Kirkpatrick, Ralph; Kraus, Greta; Moran, Robert, 1937-; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Nandi, Jean; Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695; Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764; Reller, Austin; Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788; Clementi, Muzio, 1752-1832; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Fabrizio, Margaret; Couperin, François, 1668-1733; Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759
  - Heinitz and Ehlers concert, Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, 1960-07-14; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 36)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonata No.1, 3rd movement. Heinitz, viola de gamba; Ehlers, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. July 14, 1960.
    Suite in A. Heinitz, viola de gamba; Ehlers, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. July 14, 1960.
    Gamba suite. Heinitz, viola de gamba; Ehlers, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. July 14, 1960.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Chromatische Fantasie und Fuge. Heinitz, viola de gamba; Ehlers, harpsichord. Hertz Hall, University of California, Berkeley, CA. July 14, 1960.
    Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Heinitz, Eva; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750
  - Ehlers and Hamilton harpsichord concert, 1964-03-14; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; stereo] (Box 9, Reel 37)
    Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Hamilton, Malcolm
  - Warren Wilson College Music Department presents George Lucktenberg, 1971-12-12; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; mono] (Box 9, Reel 38)
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin en concerts. Selections. Lucktenberg, harpsichord. Bannerman Hall, Warren Wilson College. December 12, 1971.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 3e livre. Selections. Lucktenberg, harpsichord. Bannerman Hall, Warren Wilson College. December 12, 1971.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Französische Ouvertüre, B minor. Lucktenberg, harpsichord. Bannerman Hall, Warren Wilson College. December 12, 1971.
    Couperin, François, 1668-1733. Pièces de clavecin, 1er livre. No 3. Favorite. Lucktenberg, harpsichord. Bannerman Hall, Warren Wilson College. December 12, 1971.
    Couperin, Louis, approximately 1626-1661. Chaconne. Lucktenberg, harpsichord. Bannerman Hall, Warren Wilson College. December 12, 1971.
    Chambonnières, Jacques Champion de, approximately 1602-approximately 1672. Chaconnes, keyboard instrument, B. 123, G major. Lucktenberg, harpsichord. Bannerman Hall, Warren Wilson College. December 12, 1971.
    Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764; Lucktenberg, George; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Chambonnières, Jacques Champion de, approximately1602-approximately1672; Couperin, François, 1668-1733; Couperin, Louis, approximately1626-1661
  - Bach: Goldberg Variations; Canons, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; two track] (Box 10, Reel 39)
    Research note
    According to the University of California "University Bulletin" (Vol.24, No. 23), May 24, 1976, Professor Alan Curtis had recently premiered "a complete set of 14 canons recently discovered as additions to Bach's Goldberg Variations." This is likely a recording of this premiere concert.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Canons. Curtis, harpsichord.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Goldberg-Variationen. Curtis, harpsichord.
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Curtis, Alan
  - Hansen and Trimborn harpsichord recital, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips] (Box 10, Reel 40)
    Side one includes works by Scarlatti, Bach, and Stravinsky.
    Trimborn, Roswitha; Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Hansen, Elisa
  - Cabrillo Festival, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 3.75 ips] (Box 10, Reel 41)
    Jongen, Joseph, 1873-1953. Fantasy on two popular walloons. The program listing in the container lists this work as Op.40. However, Op.40 is simply entitled Rondes wallonnes. This is different from the fantasy on two walloons with is in fact Op.24.
    Jongen, Joseph, 1873-1953. Concertos, piano, orchestra, op. 127. De Groote, piano. Belgian Radio Television Symphony Orchestra, Berglund, conductor.
    Jongen, Joseph, 1873-1953. Pieces, cellos (4), op. 89.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Two pieces for psaltery players.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Concertos, violin, percussion ensemble.
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003. Labrynth no. 3. Samuel, conductor.
    Jongen, Joseph, 1873-1953; Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003; Samuel, Gerhard; Orchestre symphonique de la R.T.B.F.; Groote, André de, 1940-; Berglund, Paavo, 1929-2012
  - Cabrillo 1969, 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 10, Reel 42)
  - Tosca, San Francisco, 1970-11-11; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 10, Reel 43)
    Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca
    Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924
  - Dutch composers, undated; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 10, Reel 44)
    Leeuw, Ton de, 1926-1996. Work not listed.
    Schat, Peter, 1935-2003. Entelechie I.
    Flothuis, Marius. Espressioni cordiali.
    Landré, Guillaume, 1905-1968. Permutazioni simfoniche.
    Schat, Peter, 1935-2003; Flothuis, Marius; Leeuw, Ton de, 1926-1996; Landré, Guillaume, 1905-1968
  - Puccini: Manon Lescaut, 1974-09-13; 2 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips; dolby] (Box 10, Reel 46, Reel 45)
    Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Manon Lescaut. Price, soprano. San Francisco Opera. Live radio broadcast. September 13, 1974. Opening night of the 1974 season.
    Price, Leontyne; Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924
  - Cilèa: Adriana Lecouvreur, acts 3 and 4, circa 1977; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch; 7.5 ips; dolby] (Box 10, Reel 47)
    Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Adriana Lecouvreur. Acts 3 and 4. San Francisco Opera.
    Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950